Office of Communications and Marketing Records UA252
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Faculty files, 1946 -- 2018; UA252.005; 18 Linear Feet
  - Gustafson, Dr. Alvar W. (Veterinary School), 1985-10-03 -- 1988-09; UA252.005.023.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Gute, David (Engineering), 1993-08 -- 1993-08; UA252.005.023.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Guterman, Martin M. (Liberal Arts/Math), 1966-10-01 -- 2004-02-06; UA252.005.023.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Gutierrez, Mauricio (Liberal Arts/Math), 1979-02-26 -- 1979-03-05; UA252.005.023.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Gutterson, Wilder (Development), 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.023.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Guysinsky, Misha (Mathematics), 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.023.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Haas, Terry E. (Liberal Arts/Chemistry), 1963-09-18 -- 1988-01-21; UA252.005.023.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Haffajee, Dr. Charles (Medical School), 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.023.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Hahn, Majorie G. (Liberal Arts/Matematics), 1983-12-01 -- 1987-10-30; UA252.005.023.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Hahn, Tomie (Music), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.023.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Hallowell, Burton, 1976 -- 1977; UA252.005.023.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Halus, Siegfried (Liberal Arts/Fine Arts), 1975 -- 1986-03-04; UA252.005.023.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 44)
  - Hamer, Davidson H. (Medical), 1997-06-03 -- 1997-06-06; UA252.005.023.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 45)
  - Hammer, David (Education), 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.023.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 46)
  - Hammock, John (Nutrition), 1997-01-28 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 47)
  - Haefeli, Evan (History), 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.023.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 48)
  - Hampton, Henry, 1994 -- 1996; UA252.005.023.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 49)
  - Hannum, Hurst (Fletcher), 1991-11-21 -- 1994-08-22; UA252.005.023.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 50)
  - Hanes, N. Bruce, 1963-02 -- 1990-09; UA252.005.023.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 51)
  - Hansch, Steven (Nutrition), 1989-06 -- 1989-06; UA252.005.023.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 52)
  - Harder, David (Liberal Arts/Psychology), 1982-02-05 -- 1985-04; UA252.005.023.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 53)
  - Jalal, Ayesha (history), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.023.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 54)
  - Jansen, Daniel (Civil Engineering), 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.023.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 55)
  - Jennings, James (UEPP), 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.023.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 56)
  - Jennings, Michael (education), 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 57)
  - Johansen, Erling (Dental School), 1976-03-20 -- 2008-04-28; UA252.005.023.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 58)
  - John, James A. (Music), 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.023.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 59)
  - Johnson, Eric (Development), 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.023.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 60)
  - Johnson, Ronna, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.023.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 61)
  - Johnson, Virginia (Drama), 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.023.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 62)
  - Johnston, Sybil (English), 2001-03 -- 2001-03; UA252.005.023.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 63)
  - Jones, Royden (Medical), 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.023.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 64)
  - Josa-Jones, Paula (Liberal Arts/Dance), 1987-05-14 -- 1988-01-21; UA252.005.023.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 65)
  - Joseph, Paul (Liberal Arts/Sociology), 1977-12-13 -- 1987-01-15; UA252.005.023.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 66)
  - Kaczmarczyk, Alexander (Liberal Arts/Chemistry), 1968-10 -- 1987-09-10; UA252.005.023.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 67)
  - Kaitin, Kenneth I. (CTR Study Drug Develop), 1987-10-08 -- 2000; UA252.005.023.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 68)
  - Kaminer, Michael (Medical), 1997-03-03 -- 1997-03-03; UA252.005.023.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 69)
  - Kaminishi, Ikumi (Art History), 1996-10-17 -- 1996-10-17; UA252.005.023.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 70)
  - Kanarek, Robin (Liberal Arts/Psychology), 1977-03 -- 2003; UA252.005.023.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 71)
  - Kane, Dr. Anne (Medical School), 1990-04 -- 1996-07-09; UA252.005.023.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 72)
  - Kaplan, David L. (Chem. Engineering), 1996-10-21 -- 2001; UA252.005.023.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 73)
  - Kaplan, Dr. Gary, 1980 -- 1995; UA252.005.023.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 74)
  - Kaplan, Dr. Marshall M> (Medical School), 1981-06-11 -- 1997-05-14; UA252.005.023.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 75)
  - Kaplan, Sherrie H. (Medical School), 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.023.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 76)
  - Karas, Alicia (Veterinary), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.023.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 77)
  - Karlin, Dr. Lawrence (Medical School), 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.023.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 78)
  - Karmody, Dr. Colin S., 1983-10-27 -- 1993; UA252.005.023.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 79)
  - Karp, Dr. David (Medical School), 1986 -- 1987-03; UA252.005.023.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 80)
  - Kassirer, Dr. Jerome P. (Medical School), 1980-08 -- 2001; UA252.005.023.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 81)
  - Katz, Dr. Arnold E. (Medical School), 1982-12-02 -- 1983; UA252.005.023.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 82)
  - Kauer, John S. Ph. D. (Medical School), 1987-01-29 -- 1997-04-18; UA252.005.023.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 83)
  - Kawamura, Yoshie, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.023.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 84)
  - Kelly, Erin, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.023.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 85)
    Bio paragraph
  - Kelley, Paul, 1992 -- 1994; UA252.005.023.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 86)
  - Kennedy, Eileen, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.023.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 87)
    emails
  - Kennison, Robert, 1981 -- 1988; UA252.005.023.00088; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 88)
    photos/publication order sheet
  - Kenny, Jonathan E., 1985 -- 1995; UA252.005.023.00089; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 89)
    photos/newspaper clippings/resume/newsletter
  - Keusch, Gerald, 1986 -- 1996; UA252.005.023.00090; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 90)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press release
  - Khan, Nasir, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.023.00091; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 91)
  - Kiez, Debra, 1994 -- 1994; UA252.005.023.00092; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 92)
  - Kilmer, Misha Elena, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.023.00093; 1 Folder(s) (Box 23, Folder 93)
  - Kim, Bruce, 1996 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 1)
    photos/press release/biography paragraph
  - King, Andrew, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.024.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - King, Joan C., 1980 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - King, William J., 1965 -- 1982; UA252.005.024.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 4)
    photos/newspaper clippings/fact sheet/faculty news/personnel record
  - Kirker-head, Carl, 1987 -- 2000; UA252.005.024.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 5)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases/event program/interview transcript
  - Kirshen, Paul, 2003 -- 2003; UA252.005.024.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Kisliuk, Roy L., 1986 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Klauber, George, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Kleine, Lawrence J., 1982 -- 1982; UA252.005.024.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Klema, Ernest D., 1968 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 10)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases/letters/biographical data sheet/curriculum vitae
  - Klempner, Mark, 1983 -- 2000; UA252.005.024.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 11)
    photos/newspaper clippings/ press releases
  - Harrington, John, 1995 -- 2002; UA252.005.024.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 12)
    photos/press releases/ letters/ invitation
  - Harris, Burton, 1983 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Hartman, Ernest, 1976 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 14)
    photo/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/press release
  - Hasselblatt, Boris, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.024.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Hassoun, Soha, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 16)
    photo/newspaper clipping/biographical paragraph
  - Hecht, Mary, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.024.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Hecht, Norman B., 1970 -- 1995; UA252.005.024.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 18)
    photos/newspaper clippings/curriculum vitae/bio sheet/personnel record/fact sheet
  - Hayes, Catherine, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 19)
    photo/press release
  - Hedges, Thomas, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.024.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Helwege, Ann, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Henriksen, Alan K., 1974 -- 1987; UA252.005.024.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 22)
    photos/newspaper clippings/book reviews/ letters/press release/biographical info
  - Herbet, Jean English, 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Nieto-Herman, Aidee, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Herman, Ira M., 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Herrera, Haydee, 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Hess, Andrew, 1984 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Hines, Thomas, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Hinkelman, Elizabeth, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Hinrichs, Katrin, 1989 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 30)
    photos/press release/diagram
  - Hirayama, Hiroshi, 1994 -- 2014; UA252.005.024.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Hirsch, Steven W., 1980 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 32)
    newspaper clippings/biographical data sheet/book review
  - Hirata, Hosea, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Hirshman, Marcie, 1992 -- 1992; UA252.005.024.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Hitchner, Bruce, 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.024.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Ho, Shuk-mei, 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.024.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Hodge, Harold C., 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.024.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Hoffman, Andrew, 1997 -- 1998; UA252.005.024.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 38)
    photos/magazine clipping/press release
  - Holcomb, Phil, 1992 -- 1993; UA252.005.024.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Hollister, Robert, 1980 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 40)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases
  - Holzman, Franklyn, 1961 -- 1987; UA252.005.024.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 41)
    photos/newspaper clippings/letters/resume/curriculum vitae/press releases/academic papers/public information fact sheet
  - Holzman, Franklyn #2, 1986 -- 2002; UA252.005.024.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 42)
    photos/newspaper clippings/obituary/curriculum vitae
  - Holzman, Mathilda, 1966 -- 1987; UA252.005.024.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 43)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press release/biographical information/academic paper/public information fact sheet
  - Horowitz, David, 1990 -- 1992; UA252.005.024.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 44)
  - Howard, Anita, 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.024.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 45)
  - Howell, Alvin H., 1950 -- 1978; UA252.005.024.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 46)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press releases/biographical information/magazine article/event program/curriculum vitae
  - Howe, Elizabeth T., 1982 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 47)
    photos/newspaper clippings/faculty news/event program/letter/bio sheet
  - Howe, Margot C., 1979 -- 1989; UA252.005.024.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 48)
    photos/newspaper clippings/retirement resolution/curriculum vitae/academic papers
  - Hsu, George, 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.024.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 49)
  - Huber, Brigitte T., 1990 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 50)
  - Mahmoud, Muhammad A., 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - Malchow, Howard, 1992 -- 1998; UA252.005.024.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 52)
  - Mancke, Richard B., 1981 -- 1983; UA252.005.024.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 53)
  - Maness, William, 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 54)
  - Mann, Anthony, 1972 -- 2018; UA252.005.024.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 55)
  - Manning, Marjorie (Gott), 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 56)
  - Manno, Vincent P., 1986 -- 2002; UA252.005.024.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 57)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biography sheet
  - Manos, Steven S., 1981 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 58)
  - Manz, Beatriz, 1983 -- 1991; UA252.005.024.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 59)
  - Marchant, Douglas, 1980 -- 1987; UA252.005.024.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 60)
    photos/newspaper clippings/contact information
  - Marcopoulos, George J., 1966 -- 1992; UA252.005.024.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 61)
    photos/newspaper clippings/press release/public information fact sheet
  - Marder, Amy, 1987 -- 1987; UA252.005.024.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 62)
  - Marrone, Steven P., 1983 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 63)
  - Martin, Bernhard, 1996 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 64)
  - Martin, Carole, 1995 -- 1995; UA252.005.024.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 65)
    photo/newspaper clipping
  - Maskalenko, Edward J., 1972 -- 1994; UA252.005.024.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 66)
    photos/public information fact sheet/biographical blurb
  - Mason, Joel, 1980 -- 1995; UA252.005.024.00067; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 67)
  - Massler, Maury, 1979 -- 1983; UA252.005.024.00068; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 68)
    photos/newspaper clippings/magazine articles
  - Matz, Michael, 1991 -- 1991; UA252.005.024.00069; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 69)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1986 -- 2006; UA252.005.024.00070; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 70)
    photos/obituary
  - McCabe, Ina B., 1999 -- 1999; UA252.005.024.00071; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 71)
  - McCann, John, 1986 -- 1986; UA252.005.024.00072; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 72)
  - McCarthy, Kathryn A., 1946 -- 2015; UA252.005.024.00073; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 73)
    photos/newspaper clippings/event program/curriculum vitae/public information fact sheet/retirement resolution/annual report/letters/press releases/faculty notes/obituary
  - Meller, Victoria, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00074; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 74)
    photos/newspaper clippings/biographical blurb
  - Memon, Mushtaq, 1989 -- 1989; UA252.005.024.00075; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Mendelsohn, Michael, 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00076; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 76)
  - Merrigan, Kathleen, 2001 -- 2001; UA252.005.024.00077; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 77)
  - Messina, Anthony, 1987 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00078; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 78)
    photos/curriculum vitae
  - Metcalf, Gilbert, 1994 -- 2004; UA252.005.024.00079; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 79)
  - Meydani, Simin, 1989 -- 1997; UA252.005.024.00080; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 80)
  - Meyer, Klemens, 1996 -- 1996; UA252.005.024.00081; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 81)
  - Miauolis, Ioannis, 1989 -- 2003; UA252.005.024.00082; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 82)
    photos/press releases/annual report/curriculum vitae
  - Knowles, Dr. Kim (Veterinary School), 1990-05 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.024.00083; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 83)
  - Klein, Donald W. (Liberal Arts/Poly.SC.), 1972-10-02 -- 1986-09-07; UA252.005.024.00084; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 84)
  - Knable, Bobbie (Liberal Arts), 1970-09-01 -- 1985-11-14; UA252.005.024.00085; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 85)
  - Kodak, Nagi (Engineering), 1990 -- 1990; UA252.005.024.00086; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 86)
  - Kolterman, Leslie (Advancement), 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.024.00087; 1 Folder(s) (Box 24, Folder 87)
  - Konstam, Marvin A. (Medical), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.025.00001; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Kopin, Alan (Medical), 1992-12 -- 1992-12; UA252.005.025.00002; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Korn, Dr. Marcel (Dental School), 1987-09-10 -- 1990-11; UA252.005.025.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Kosch, Dr. Philip, 1996-02-13 -- 1999-04; UA252.005.025.00004; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Hume, James D. (Liberal Arts/Geology), 1963 -- 1985-06-25; UA252.005.025.00005; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Hunter, Dr. Howard E. (Liberal Arts/Religion), 1966-09 -- 1993-01-10; UA252.005.025.00006; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Hurka, Joseph (English), 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.025.00007; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Hurvitz, Dr. Kenneth (Medical School), 1975 -- 1995; UA252.005.025.00008; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Hyde, James (Medical School/Com. HLTH), 1988-01-21 -- 1996; UA252.005.025.00009; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Inouye, Charles (Administrations), 1997-06 -- 2003; UA252.005.025.00010; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Ioannides, Yannis (Economics), 1995-10-03 -- 1998-12; UA252.005.025.00011; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Isles, David F. (Liberal Arts/Mathematics), 1964-10-01 -- 1986-11-20; UA252.005.025.00012; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Isberg, Ralph R. (Medical School), 1987-01-29 -- 1998-02-15; UA252.005.025.00013; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Islam, Shafiqul (Engineering), 2004 -- 2004; UA252.005.025.00014; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Isner, Dr. Jeffrey (Medical School), 1982-09-23 -- 2001; UA252.005.025.00015; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Jacobs, Robert (EE &Computer Science), 1994-11 -- 1994-11; UA252.005.025.00016; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Jacobs, Francine (Liberal Arts/Child Study), 1986-12-04 -- 1997; UA252.005.025.00017; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Jacque, Laurent J. (Fletcher), 1997-10-29 -- 1997-10-29; UA252.005.025.00018; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Jacques, Paul (HNRC), 1986-06-19 -- 1999; UA252.005.025.00019; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Jaffe, Andy, 1992-03 -- 1992-03; UA252.005.025.00020; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Kouloyan, Valerie (Veterinary), 1998 -- 1998; UA252.005.025.00021; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Kounaves, Samuel, 1992-12 -- 2002; UA252.005.025.00022; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Kowalczyk, Carsten (Fletcher), 1995-12-13 -- 1996-06-12; UA252.005.025.00023; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Krall, Elizabeth (Dental School), 1996-09-16 -- 1996-09-16; UA252.005.025.00024; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Kramer, Gertrude (Medical School), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.025.00025; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Kraut, Dr. Joel A. (Medical School), 1986-02-06 -- 1988-01-21; UA252.005.025.00026; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Kraus, Dr. Karl (Veterinary School), 1997 -- 1997; UA252.005.025.00027; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Kream, Dr. Richard, 1992-12-30 -- 1992-12-30; UA252.005.025.00028; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Kreidberg, Dr. Marshall B. (Medical School), 1970 -- 1990; UA252.005.025.00029; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Krimsky, Sheldon (Liberal Arts/Urb & Env), 1970-11 -- 2001; UA252.005.025.00030; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Krinsky, Norman I. (Liberal Arts/Biochem), 1981-09-17 -- 2001; UA252.005.025.00031; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Kriefeldt, John G. (Liberal Arts/Engineer), 1969-01-03 -- 1987; UA252.005.025.00032; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Kritzman, Dr. Julius (Medical School), 1990-05 -- 1990-05; UA252.005.025.00033; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Kronman, Dr. Joseph (Dental School), 1985-10-15 -- 1988-01-21; UA252.005.025.00034; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Kugel, Dr. Gerard (Dental School), 1987-09-10 -- 1989; UA252.005.025.00035; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Kuhlik, Amy (Medial), 2000 -- 2000; UA252.005.025.00036; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Kuliopulos, Athan (Medical), 2002 -- 2002; UA252.005.025.00037; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Kumar, Krishna (Chemistry), 1998 -- 2003; UA252.005.025.00038; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Krume, David Ph. D. (Liberal Arts/Comp Sci.), 1985-03-25 -- 1987-11-19; UA252.005.025.00039; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Kuperwasser, C. (Medical), 2005 -- 2005; UA252.005.025.00040; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Kutsoati, Edward (Economics), 1998 -- 1999; UA252.005.025.00041; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Kuske, Rachel (Mathematics), 1996-10-03 -- 1996-10-03; UA252.005.025.00042; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Kwan, Dr. Edward (Medical School), 1980 -- 1990; UA252.005.025.00043; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Lobato, Dr. Mary (Vet. School), 1991-12 -- 1996-07-26; UA252.005.025.00044; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Lang, Ambrose Kofi (Electrical Eng.), 1999 -- 2000; UA252.005.025.00045; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Lasagna, Louis (Medical), 1996 -- 2004; UA252.005.025.00046; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Lang, Kenneth R. (Liberal Arts/Astronomy), 1976-10-01 -- 1995; UA252.005.025.00047; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Lastavica, Dr. Catherine (Meical School), 1985-07-03 -- 1994; UA252.005.025.00048; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Laurent, Pierre-Henri (Liberal Arts/Intl Relat.), 1970-09-09 -- 1994-01-13; UA252.005.025.00049; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Lau, Dr. Joseph (Medical School), 1992 -- 1997; UA252.005.025.00050; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Lash, Merilyn (Medical School), 1992-12 -- 1993; UA252.005.025.00051; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Lawler, Margaret (Medical School), 1993 -- 1993; UA252.005.025.00052; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Lawrence, Elizabeth (Veterinary School), 1982-02-14 -- 1998-08; UA252.005.025.00053; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Leav, Dr. Irwin (Veterinary School), 1982-12-16 -- 1988; UA252.005.025.00054; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Lebowitz, Dr. Alan L. (Liberal Arts/English), 1971-11-30 -- 1987-10-08; UA252.005.025.00055; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Lee, Brian K. (Vet School), 1987-11-05 -- 1999-11-16; UA252.005.025.00056; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Lee, K. Francis (Medical), 1990 -- 2000; UA252.005.025.00057; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Lee, Dr. Mary (Medical School), 1995 -- 1998-03; UA252.005.025.00058; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Leekeenan, Debbie (Child Development), 1997-08-08 -- 1997-08-08; UA252.005.025.00059; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Legler, Ken (Liberal Arts/Phys. Ed.), 1980-09-04 -- 1987-09-10; UA252.005.025.00060; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Leiter, Dr. Andrew (Medical School), 1990-04 -- 1990-04; UA252.005.025.00061; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Lerner, Richard (Child Development), 2000-03-31 -- 2000-03-31; UA252.005.025.00062; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Leskowitz, Sr. Sidney (Sackler School), 1987-11-19 -- 1987-11-19; UA252.005.025.00063; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Leupp, Gary P. (History), 1995 -- 1996-12; UA252.005.025.00064; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Le Van, Dr. Laura (Veterinary School, 1993-10 -- 1999; UA252.005.025.00065; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Levey, Andrew (Medical), 1985-06-21 -- 2000; UA252.005.025.00066; 1 Folder(s) (Box 25, Folder 66)